/*https://www.paulsquiz.com/complete-pub-quizzes-mainmenu-328/202-free-quiz-questions/73-complete-pub-quizzes/711-pub-quiz-10*/

const Questions =
        [
            {
                questionId : 0,
                questionAnswer : 'McDonalds',
                question : "Which company is the largest toy distributor in the world? ",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "McDonalds",
                        B : "Burger King",
                        C : "KFC",
                        D : "Popeyes",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 1,
                questionAnswer : 'Start Smoking',
                question : "Each day three thousand Americans do what for the first time?",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "Make Coffee",
                        B : "Start Smoking",
                        C : "Buy Guns",
                        D : "Sell Drugs",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 2,
                questionAnswer : 'Roses',
                question : "Queen Elizabeth I of England had anthrophobia. What was she afraid of?",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "Clowns",
                        B : "Donkeys",
                        C : "Pigs",
                        D : "Roses",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 3,
                questionAnswer : 'Penis',
                question : "Chachi was a character in Happy days, what does Chachi mean in Korean?",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "White",
                        B : "Sword",
                        C : "Penis",
                        D : "Knuckles",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 4,
                questionAnswer : 'Pornography',
                question : "73% of the world's what is produced and consumed in the USA?",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "Pornography",
                        B : "Cartoons",
                        C : "Funny Videos",
                        D : "Movies",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 5,
                questionAnswer : 'Beer',
                question : "Hawaiian - Pia, Polish - Piwo, Hungarian - Sor - what is it? ",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "Beer",
                        B : "Alcohol",
                        C : "Drunk",
                        D : "Alcoholic",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 6,
                questionAnswer : 'Horses',
                question : "Only humans and what other animal has hymens?",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "Pigs",
                        B : "Monkeys",
                        C : "Horses",
                        D : "Elephants",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 7,
                questionAnswer : 'Japan',
                question : "Fried Chicken followed by Strawberry Shortcake is the traditional Christmas Eve meal in which country?",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "Greek",
                        B : "Turkey",
                        C : "Japan",
                        D : "USA",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 8,
                questionAnswer : 'Halifax, Nova Scotia',
                question : "What Canadian city has the most bars per capita?",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "Halifax, Nova Scotia",
                        B : "Prince Edward Island",
                        C : "Darmouth",
                        D : "Sydney",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 9,
                questionAnswer : 'Black Sabbath',
                question : "What pop group famously said 'We're only in it for the volume'? ",
                answers :
                    {
                        A : "Black Sabbath",
                        B : "Metallica",
                        C : "U2",
                        D : "BonJovi",
                    }
            },
            {
                questionId : 10,
            },
        ]


export default Questions